I'm not... letting anyone kill me.
It really is a desert.
Wh-What the hell is that thing?!
No!
What the hell?
What am I even supposed to do?
Answer me, Subaru Natsuki!
No! No! No!
Someone... Someone help me!
I'm underneath... the desert?
Shit...
Shit, shit, shit!
What the hell?! What the hell?!
What the hell do you want from me?!
That's the third one.
How long has it been?
Three hours? Four hours?
Ow...
Damn it!
Screw you!
Why?! Why do you have to be in my way?!
Wh... What the...
Damn it, stop screwing with me!
Huh?
I did all that running...
and running... and running...
I'm done.
I'll just kill you.
I don't know who you are...
but I'll kill you.
I swear I'm gonna kill you.
Kill you... Kill you... Kill you...
Kill you...
Kill you, kill you, kill you, kill you,
kill you, kill you, kill you, kill you...
So... it wasn't Shaula, then...
Beatrice and Meili are kids.
They'd be easy.
Emilia didn't seem that wary of me.
In that sense, the most dangerous
ones are Ram and Echidna.
Julius, too.
It'd be great if he'd
just die on his own...
Huh?
The only ones I haven't seen
are Emilia and Beatrice.
One of those two is—
Oh, it's you?
Stop following me!
I don't have time to play with you!
I have to kill everyone who's still alive!
If you're gonna get in my way, then...
Damn it!
Damn it! Damn it, damn it, damn it!
What the hell?! What the hell is this?!
You and all the others...
the dead bodies and
the ones who are alive...
What the hell are you thinking?!
What are you trying to do?!
I don't give a shit about any of you!
You're all just shoving
your problems onto me!
If you're all so
preoccupied with yourselves,
what about me?!
I'm busy with my own damn problems, too!
Why can't you just... leave me alone?
Just leave me all by myself!
Ow! Are you—
No!
I don't wanna die!
Lizard!
What... the...
Just what the hell are you?
Try to figure it out next time,
hero.
Subaru!
Hey, Subaru! Are you all right?
Emi...lia...
Oh, what a relief!
I was so worried about you!
Subaru?
What is it?
He's still half-asleep, I suppose.
How very easygoing, especially
after he worried us so much.
You!
I'm not happy with this, I suppose!
Emilia and Betty were
the ones who found him!
Now, don't sulk.
What's wrong with it? Subaru
and Patrasche are really close.
Hey, Subaru...
Are you sure you're feeling all right?
Yeah, I'm totally fine. No prob.
I guess all the tiredness
finally got to me.
People fall asleep all the time, y'know?
I see...
But when you feel tired, tell us.
You mustn't push yourself too hard.
It's gonna make things risky,
but I won't tell them about
my memory loss this time.
I want to find out if it's connected
to the reason I keep getting killed.
Frankly, I could see killing someone over
something you don't want them to remember,
but it's hard to imagine killing
someone because they forgot something.
Subaru.
You've got that wrinkle
on your forehead again.
What did I do for her to get
that close with me, anyway?
I didn't find their bodies, but...
Try to figure it out next time,
hero.
That voice didn't belong
to either of them.
In fact, no one in this group sounds like—
Barusu.
Stop spacing out and help me fetch water.
Oops, sorry.
I hear you were sleeping in the archive.
You shouldn't try anything stupid.
You'll only trouble those around you.
Yeah, I know I shouldn't have done it.
Sorry for making you worry, too.
Worry about you? Why would I?
For my safety, I guess?
Good morning, Master!
Did you sleep well last night?
I slept great, thanks for asking!
I had a dream about the past, actually!
It was you and me, and my mom, and...
Okay, okay, I get it. You
can tell me about it later.
Anyway, did you notice anything about
me when you saw me this morning?
This morning?
You looked as sexy as ever!
I've been waiting 400
years for you to propose!
You've got some real patience.
Well, if you didn't notice
anything, it's all good.
Really?
Shaula, I have a favor to ask.
Huh? What is it?
Julius.
I want to talk about what
happened last night.
Just the two of us, you know?
About... last night?
I thought that conversation was over.
Do you disagree?
Yeah, I sure do.
I wasn't satisfied with
that in the slightest.
Satisfied, eh?
I see. That's very like you.
But do you not feel that's
a bit too selfish of you?
You don't look satisfied
with how it ended, either.
We're both holding on to
something that pisses us off,
and you expect me to just live with it?
Like hell I can.
Well, then, what other choice do we have?
My feelings are exactly
as I told you last night.
I have nothing further to say.
Because I knew nothing at all of the
secret between you and Lady Anastasia—
that is, you and Echidna.
The secret... between me and Echidna?
I understand that you meant no harm.
And I spoke with Echidna,
though not nearly enough.
She can be trusted.
Rather, there is no other
option but to trust her.
If I hope to save Lady Anastasia,
then I have to bet on the possibility.
Even if we get her back
and she doesn't remember who I am...
What... do you mean?
Honestly...
Please don't make me feel any
more pathetic in your presence.
When you mentioned what happened
last night, it frightened me a bit.
I didn't know what I would
do if you apologized to me.
If I... apologized?
If you had, how would I have responded?
There's no way to know now, however.
Master, you sure you want
to leave things like that?
Yeah.
Seems like Julius had nothing to do
with what happened in the archive.
Except now he's even more suspicious
of who I was yesterday.
I don't really get it,
but was I useful to you?
Yeah. You totally were.
I was able to confront Julius without
fear because you were there.
Glad to hear it!
Well, then, Master, Master...
I want a big hug as a reward!
Not doing that.
What?! That's so mean!
You said you'd give me any reward I wanted
as long as it wasn't way out of bounds!
And that goes beyond the
boundaries of my innocence.
So just what were you doing to be
targeted and by whom, Subaru Natsuki?
I'm stuck at an impasse.
I'm starting to think
I should ask Patrasche.
What? The land dragon?
I don't like her. She keeps glaring at me.
Hey! I won't let you badmouth Patrasche!
Even if badmouthing anyone was acceptable,
Patrasche is the only one
I won't let you badmouth!
Master, just how much has that
land dragon emasculated you?
So on that note, you and I are done here.
See ya.
What?! You just turned a
blind eye to my reward!
But I will not lose heart!
To be a woman who's convenient
to you is my reason for living!
What about Subaru Natsuki
makes him worth all that?
Master?
Oh, damn it!
You don't have to think about
being convenient to me.
I'm sorry.
Master...
Having you there with me
was a big help. That's all.
Master...
At long last...
you're ready to love me?!
My boundaries!
If the way they all acted was phony,
I don't know what I'm supposed to believe.
I guess Patrasche really is
the only one I can trust.
Maybe I'd be happier living in a
paradise for just me and her—
Uh-oh. I heard that.
Wha?!
So you want to run somewhere
far away with Patrasche?
Beatrice and Big Sister would
cry if they heard that.
It was just a bad joke.
Forget about it. In every sense.
Yeah, sure.
But even if that's how you really
feel, I won't laugh at you.
I've lived with mabeasts
all my life, remember?
Mabeasts...
So it's kinda like you
were raised by wolves?
You said that yesterday, too.
My mom was incredibly strict.
And Elsa, the one I was around
all the time, was really lax,
so there was a lot I had to take care of.
Okay, wait, wait! You keep putting
more and more holes in my brain!
Look, I'm busy right now.
Go play with Shaula or something.
The half-naked lady?
I'm fine with that,
but you're the one I have
business with right now.
Me?
What you said yesterday...
How seriously should I take that?
Ow...
What is this?
You're kidding me...
No way! No way! No way!
No way!
Meili!
Hey! Meili!
Meili! Meili!
Damn it!
Damn it! Damn it!
I...
killed her?
But why... would I...
Subaru Natsuki Was Here
Empty Shell